https://steel.fivesgroup.com/footer-pages/legal-notice.html

Jump to content
Skip to navigation
Why us?
Why us?
Menu
Why us?
Why us?
Legal notice
Please read carefully the Terms of Use including Legal Notice and Privacy Policy of the website www.fivesgroup.com, before continuing browsing.
The website www.fivesgroup.com is the exclusive property of FIVES, Société Anonyme (limited company) with an Executive Board and Supervisory Board and a share capital of € 102,723,764.00, registered in RCS Paris under number 542 023 841, and having it registered address at 3 rue Drouot 75009 Paris, France, hereinafter referred to as "FIVES".
The web hosting company of www.fivesgroup.com is Fives Information Technology & Systems, 3 rue Drouot 75009 Paris, France.
The following terms shall be construed in the Legal Notice and Privacy Policy according to the following definitions: "Website" means website www.fivesgroup.com, including all content such as text, graphics, photo, graphics, sounds, data, images, software, etc. owned by FIVES or licensed to FIVES; "Website Material" means software, services, features, news and more generally all elements and data included on the Website; and  "User" means any person accessing the Website and browsing the public areas of the Website.
LEGAL NOTICE
The Website is provided by FIVES for information only and should not be relied upon or used as the sole basis for making decisions without consulting primary, more accurate, more complete or more timely sources of information. By accessing and downloading any Website Material, you agree to be bound by this Legal Notice as if you had signed them. In case of disagreement with this Legal Notice, please do not access or use this Website.
You hereby acknowledge and agree with the following: FIVES is the owner of the website accessible at the following address www.fivesgroup.com This Legal Notice constitutes the agreement between FIVES and each User accessing or using the Website.  1. Time
This Legal Notice and future amendments shall remain valid as long as they are available on the Website.
2. Services on Website
The Website is available 24 hours on 24, 7 days on 7.
FIVES wishes to maintain constant improvement of the services available on the Website. Accordingly, FIVES can make any necessary changes in the services available on the Website. Using services offered on the Website will be deemed as an acceptance by the User of the modified services available on the Website.
FIVES reserves the right to occasionally interrupt any services on the Website without justification, or suspend access to the Website for whatever reason, at any time and without prior notice.
The User hereby accepts to waive any recourse against FIVES for any consequences as a result of interruption or suspension of the Website regardless of its duration.
3. Property / Right of use
FIVES is the owner or has been granted any necessary rights with respect to any Website Material.
FIVES shall grant the User a worldwide, non-exclusive, non-transferable, and limited right to use the Website. The User may access, copy, download and print the Website Material for its use, provided that the User does not modify or delete any copyright, trademark or other proprietary notice that appears on such Website Material. Any other use of content on the Website, including but not limited to the modification, distribution, transmission, performance, broadcast, publication, uploading, licensing, reverse engineering, transfer or sale of, or the creation of derivative works from, any Website Material, information, software, products or services obtained from the Website, or use of the Website for purposes, is expressly prohibited.
No license and no right other than to consult the Website is granted to the User. In particular, the User is not entitled to modify, in any manner whatsoever, translate or incorporate all or part of the Website. In addition, distinctive signs, including but not limited to company names, logos, products and brands mentioned on the Website or contained in the Website Material are the property of FIVES. They cannot be used without the prior written agreement of FIVES. The User continues to hold the rights related to the elements that he may transmit to FIVES through the Website.
The User who provides information to FIVES hereby grants to FIVES an unrestricted, non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable and fully sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute and display such information throughout the world in any media. Such information will be considered non-confidential. Consequently, the user grants FIVES for the duration of this Legal Notice, and in accordance with the same, worldwide, non-exclusive, non-transferable, rights to reproduce and present on digital media the elements of the site as well as all distinctive signs such as trademarks and logos.
4. Material provided by the User
The User guarantees to Fives that: information, data and other elements supplied on the Website are accurate, current, complete, and decent; it is authorized to provide such information, data and other elements; and the information, data and other elements provided on the Website are not subject to the rights of any third party and in particular do not infringe pre-existing rights of any third party.  The User shall indemnify and hold FIVES harmless from any suit or action, objection and opposition for breach by the User of the foregoing guarantee. The User will shall indemnify and hold FIVES harmless from any suit or action of any third party for wrong or misleading nature of the information posted on the Website by the User.
The User shall not use the tools and features of the Website inaccurately, upload any software viruses through documents or programs, or act in such a manner that could create damage, interfere with or copy software, data or information from the Website.
5. Disclaimer
ACCESSING AND BROWSING ON THE WEBSITE SHALL BE AT THE SOLE RISK OF THE USER.
THE WEBSITE AND THE WEBSITE MATERIAL ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE". THE WEBSITE MAY CONTAIN INACCURACIES OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS.
FIVES EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND ANY WARRANTIES THAT WEBSITE MATERIAL ARE NONINFRINGING, AS WELL AS WARRANTIES IMPLIED FROM A COURSE OF PERFORMANCE OR COURSE OF DEALING; THAT ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE WILL BE ERROR-FREE; THAT THE WEBSITE WILL BE SECURE; THAT THE WEBSITE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE WEBSITE AVAILABLE WILL BE VIRUS-FREE; OR THAT INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE WILL BE COMPLETE, ACCURATE OR TIMELY.
IF THE USER DOWNLOADS ANY WEBSITE MATERIAL, THE USER MAY DO SO AT ITS OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. THE USER WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO ITS COMPUTER SYSTEM OR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH WEBSITE MATERIAL. NO ADVICE OR INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY THE USER FROM FIVES OR THROUGH OR FROM THE WEBSITE SHALL CREATE ANY WARRANTY OF ANY KIND. FIVES DOES NOT MAKE ANY WARRANTIES OR REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OF THE WEBSITE MATERIAL IN TERMS OF THEIR COMPLETENESS, CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, ADEQUACY, USEFULNESS, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY OR OTHERWISE. FIVES MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THE WEBSITE AND TO PARTS OF THE WEBSITE AT ANY TIME WITHOUT NOTICE.
FIVES RESERVES THE RIGHT TO RESTRICT OR TERMINATE THE USER’S ACCESS TO THE WEBSITE OR ANY FEATURE OR PART THEREOF AT ANY TIME.
6. Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL FIVES BE LIABLE TO THE USER FOR LOSS OF PRODUCTION, LOSS OF REVENUE, LOSS OF PROFIT, LOSS OF BUSINESS, LOSS OF REPUTATION OR OPPORTUNITY AND ANY OTHER PURELY FINANCIAL LOSS, OR FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, INDIRECT AND/OR CONSEQUENTIAL LOSS AND/OR DAMAGE OF ANY NATURE ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR AS A RESULT OF THE WEBSITE, HOWSOEVER CAUSED AND WHETHER SUCH LIABILITY ARISES UNDER CONTRACT, TORT (INCLUDING NEGLIGENCE), STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE EVEN IF FIVES HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGE OR LOSS.
THE USER ACKNOWLEDGES THAT FIVES, AS WELL AS ITS CONTENT AND SERVICE PROVIDERS (AND IN PARTICULAR THE WEB HOSTING COMPANY) SHALL IN NO EVENT BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO THE USER ARISING DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY FOR (I) DISSEMINATION OF FALSE INFORMATION, OR (II) ANY DELAY IN THE DELIVERY OF WEBSITE SERVICE AND/OR INFORMATION DISSEMINATION, CAUSED BY DEFECTS AFFECTING WEBSITE, INTERRUPTIONS OR CONNECTION, FRAUDULENT ACTIONS OF ANY THIRD PARTIES.
FIVES SHALL NOT BE HELD RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONSEQUENCES RESULTING FROM IMPROPER OR FRAUDULENT USE OF THE WEBSITE.
USER SHALL WAIVE ALL RIGHTS OF RECOURSE AGAINST FIVES FOR ANY DAMAGES, COSTS, EXPENSES BASED ON A MISUNDERSTANDING OR LACK OF KNOWLEDGE OF THE LEGAL NOTICE OR THE USE OF THE WEBSITE MATERIAL.
7. Miscellaneous
If any of the provisions of this Legal Notice is found to be void and unenforceable, such provision shall be deemed to be deleted from this Legal Notice and the remaining provisions of this Legal Notice shall continue in full force and effect.
8. Applicable Law
The laws of France shall govern this Legal Notice and the use by the User of the Website.
9. Disputes
The Commercial Court (Tribunal de Commerce) of in Paris, France, shall have exclusive jurisdiction over any dispute arising out of this legal notice or any action relating to the enforcement of its provisions.
10. Commitment of the User
The User shall refrain from any act which are detrimental to the privacy or reputation of others or any other person, and shall avoid comment, message or text defamatory, provocative, malicious or threatening.
The User of the Website, when providing information and data to FIVES through the Website, guarantees the accuracy and correctness of such information and data provided to the Website, and is fully empowered and authorized to provide the same.
Any use of the Website is always subject to compliance with applicable law and any failure to comply with applicable law may lead to prosecution.
PRIVACY POLICY
1. General Provisions
This Privacy Policy is part of the Legal Notice of the website and shall apply to any user of www.fivesgroup.com. This Privacy Policy describes the processing related to personal data which may be collected by FIVES when the user has access and uses the Website.
2. Definitions and personal data collection
By using the website and providing personal information, the user consents to the collection and use of their personal data according to this personal data Privacy Policy.
FIVES determines the purposes and means of the personal data processing and therefore acts as controller in accordance with the regulations applicable to personal data and in particular the Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data (General Data Protection Regulation “GDPR”).
"Personal data" is defined as any information relating to a directly or indirectly identified or identifiable person, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, first name, email address, IP address, etc.
"Personal data processing" is defined as any operation or collection of operations carried out with or without the use of automated procedures and applied to data or collections of data of a personal nature, such as collection, recording, organizing, storing, modification, consultation, use, distribution, deletion, destruction, etc.
A "purpose" is defined as the aim pursued by the implementation of processing, the reason for which the data are collected.
Applying a transparent approach, personal data are collected and processed in a fair and lawful manner. The collected data are suitable, relevant and not excessive in relation to the purpose for which they are collected.
These purposes are mainly the creation of a contact, an applicant profile, or a search agent on the recruitment pages.
Data collected in this way by FIVES are retained for a limited duration determined by the purpose of the processing, regulatory requirements, the recommendations of the supervisory authority.
3. Required or optional
Information identified as required, particularly in the contact form or on the recruitment pages, is essential for processing your request or application. Its status as required or optional is shown during collection. If the information is incomplete, FIVES will not be able to respond to your request.
4. Appointing a Data Protection Officer
FIVES has chosen freely to appoint a Data Protection Officer (DPO) as guarantor of FIVES' compliance with personal data protection regulations.
5. User rights
The user has a right of access, to rectification, to erasure, to object, to restriction of processing, to data portability. Right of access to data: the user may make a direct request to FIVES for information about data and processing affecting them; Right to rectification: if FIVES is holding obsolete or incorrect data, the user may request the rectification of incorrect, incomplete, ambiguous or expired data; Right to erasure (right to be forgotten): the user may ask FIVES to delete their personal data if they are not necessary or for any other reason stipulated in law; Right to object to use: the user may object, at any time and no cost, to processing of their data, pursuant to legal provisions and particularly when their data are processed for direct marketing purposes; Right to restriction: the user also has the right to limit the processing of their data, pursuant to legal provisions; Right to data portability: the user has the right to receive their personal data in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format (this right applies only to cases where the personal data is provided by the user and processed with their consent or for the execution of a contract). Finally, the user has a right of decision over the disposal of their data post-mortem.
These rights can be exercised, provided that the person justifies their identity, on simple written request sent by e-mail to the following address DPO@fivesgroup.com or by post to the Data Protection Officer at the following address: Fives, 3 Rue Drouot, 75009 Paris.
The user has the right to lodge a complaint with the supervisory authority of their country.
In France, the supervisory authority is the “Commission Nationale Informatique et Libertés (CNIL)” reachable online on www.cnil.fr/fr/plaintes or by mail at the following address: 3 Place de Fontenoy - TSA 80715 - 75334 PARIS CEDEX 07.
The contact information of the European supervisory authorities of the countries in which FIVES operates is available on the "Data Privacy" page of this website.
6. Recipients of personal data
The user is informed, prior to the collection of their data, that their data can be transmitted to partners acting as Processor (as defined in GDPR) in the execution of the data processing of the personal data concerned by this collection.
The data collected is only intended for the use of the internal services of FIVES companies. The personal data collected is not subject to any communication to external third parties. FIVES does not sell personal data to third parties.
FIVES reserves the right to report to the authorities any activity on the website of a user that may be illegal and to disclose any information about users of the site to meet legal requirements.
7. Cookies
When the user visits the FIVES website, cookies may be installed on their device (computer, tablet or smartphone), for a maximum period of 13 months from their installation.
Different cookie types used on our website:
- Traffic counter cookies
These are Google Analytics cookies which track the user's visit, to establish traffic statistics and monitor the performance of the website and each of its pages. These data enable FIVES to enhance and improve flow in the user's experience of the website. These cookies require your consent. On your first visit to one of our websites, a banner appears on the arrival page and a clickable link can be used to refuse installation of traffic counter cookies. Continuing to navigate to another page on the website or selecting an item on the website (picture, link, search button, etc.) constitutes your acceptance of the installation of these cookies on your device. If you refuse the installation of these cookies, they will not be installed on your device.
- Cookies promoting job offers on the dedicated recruitment pages
These cookies, with a maximum life of 12 months, promote job offers to candidates who visit the dedicated recruitment pages of the FIVES website.
The user may oppose the installation of all cookie types using their browser settings (if their browser has this functionality). Refusal to authorise certain cookies may impair the proper functioning of the website.
8. Links to other websites
FIVES Website contains links to other websites owned by any third party for whom FIVES has no control on the content and where FIVES cannot be held liable.
FIVES cannot be held responsible for the processing of personal data, the content and the use of any websites owned by any third party or any link contained in a linked website, or any changes or updates to such websites and to which access by the user shall be at his own risk and peril.
The user is requested by FIVES to study the processing of personal data, applied to the website owned by any external third parties and also check the terms of the processing of personal data when the user clicks or interacts with a link leading to a website owned by any external third party.
9. Modification
FIVES shall have the right to update and amend the provisions of this Privacy Policy when FIVES deems necessary and without prior notice. The user is invited to read on time to time basis the terms of this Privacy Policy.
